[{
    "Question": "<article>",
    "Answer": "Defines an article in the document"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<aside>",
    "Answer": "Defines content aside from the page content"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<bdi>",
    "Answer": "Defines a part of text that might be formatted in a different direction from other text"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<details>",
    "Answer": "Defines additional details that the user can view or hide"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<dialog>",
    "Answer": "Defines a dialog box or window"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<figcaption>",
    "Answer": "Defines a caption for a <figure> element"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<figure>",
    "Answer": "Defines self-contained content, like illustrations, diagrams, photos, code listings, etc."
  },
  {
    "Question": "<footer>",
    "Answer": "Defines a footer for the document or a section"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<header>",
    "Answer": "Defines a header for the document or a section"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<main>",
    "Answer": "Defines the main content of a document"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<mark>",
    "Answer": "Defines marked or highlighted text"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<menuitem> ",
    "Answer": "Defines a command/menu item that the user can invoke from a popup menu"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<meter>",
    "Answer": "Defines a scalar measurement within a known range (a gauge)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<nav>",
    "Answer": "Defines navigation links in the document"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<progress>",
    "Answer": "Defines the progress of a task"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<rp>",
    "Answer": "Defines what to show in browsers that do not support ruby annotations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<rt>",
    "Answer": "Defines an explanation/pronunciation of characters (for East Asian typography)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<ruby>",
    "Answer": "Defines a ruby annotation (for East Asian typography)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<section>",
    "Answer": "Defines a section in the document"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<summary>",
    "Answer": "Defines a visible heading for a <details> element"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<time>",
    "Answer": "Defines a date/time"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<wbr>",
    "Answer": "Defines a possible line-break"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<datalist>",
    "Answer": "Defines pre-defined options for input controls"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<keygen>",
    "Answer": "Defines a key-pair generator field (for forms)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<output>",
    "Answer": "Defines the result of a calculation"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Empty",
    "Answer": "<input type="
  },
  {
    "Question": "Unquoted",
    "Answer": "<input type="
  },
  {
    "Question": "Double-quoted",
    "Answer": "<input type="
  },
  {
    "Question": "Single-quoted",
    "Answer": "<input type="
  },
  {
    "Question": "<canvas>",
    "Answer": "Draw graphics, on the fly, via scripting (usually JavaScript)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<svg>",
    "Answer": "Draw scalable vector graphics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<audio>",
    "Answer": "Defines sound content"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<embed>",
    "Answer": "Defines containers for external applications (like plug-ins)"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<source>",
    "Answer": "Defines sources for <video> and <audio>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<track>",
    "Answer": "Defines tracks for <video> and <audio>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "<video>",
    "Answer": "Defines video or movie content"
  }
]
